# Morteza Shoushtari

Graduate Research Assistant

≤ shoushtari.morteza@live.com

 $\Box$  +1 (385) 450-9843

www.mshoushtari.com

in linkedin.com/in/morteza-shoushtari

#### SUMMARY

I am a Ph.D. student in the department of Electrical and Computer Engineering (ECE), Brigham Young University. Currently, I am working on physical layer security, and secure error-correction coding. I received an M.Sc. degree in Information Technology from Shiraz University, Iran, in 2013, and I have around 6 years of work experience as an IT administrator and network engineer in big companies such as Huawei Technologies Co. and JYAN Construction Co.

## RESEARCH INTERESTS

- Computer Networks
- Cloud Computing
- Physical Layer Security
- Secrecy/Error-Correction Coding

### EDUCATION

Ph.D., Computer Engineering

Dissertation topic: Secure Error-Correction Coding

Brigham Young University, Utah, USA

• Years: 2019 - 2023 (expected)

• GPA: 3.74/4

M.Sc., Information Technology (IT) Shiraz University, Shiraz, IRAN

• Years: 2011 - 2013

B.Sc., Computer Engineering

Sadjad University of Technology, Mashhad, IRAN

• Years: 2006 - 2010

#### Publication

- Morteza Shoushtari and Willie Harrison, "Secrecy coding in the Integrated Network Enhanced Telemetry (iNET)" in Proceedings of the International Telemetry Conference (ITC), Las Vegas, NV, US, Oct. 2021.
- Morteza Shoushtari and Willie Harrison, "New Dual Relationships for Error-Correcting Wiretap Codes" in Proceedings of IEEE Information Theory Workshop (ITW), Kanazawa, Japan, Oct. 2021.
- Willie Harrison and Morteza Shoushtari, "On Caching with Finite Blocklength Coding for Secrecy over the Binary Erasure Wiretap Channel" in Proceedings of IEEE Wireless Telecommunications Symposium (WTS), San Francisco, US, Apr. 2021.

## Work Experiences

# Brigham Young University, UTAH, USA

Jan 2019 - present

Graduate Research Assistant

• RA with the emphasize on physical layer security and secrecy/error-correction codes

## ${\bf IT\ Dep.\ HUAWEI\ Company,\ Tehran,\ Iran}$

Aug 2016 - Aug 2017

IT Administrator

• Maintained communication networks, monitor network performance, and resolved any technical issues

- Provided 24\*7 level one support over 850 clients
- Installed and configured network devices, including routers, switches, wireless AP's, camera's, and video conferences
- Strong contribution in Huawei IT department in Middle-East region

## IT Dep. JYAN Company, Tehran, Iran

Jan 2016 - Aug 2016

## Network Engineer

- Maintained communication networks, monitor network performance, and resolved any technical issues
- Provided 24\*7 level one support over 180 clients
- Installed and configured network devices, including routers, switches, wireless AP's, camera's, and video conferences

#### IT Dep. Persia Cloud Company, Tehran, Iran Jun 2015 - Jan 2016 Network Engineer

- Installed and configured 2X and IIRAS cloud platforms (IIAS, PAAS)
- Installed and configured Microsoft Servers (CRM, SharePoint, Lync)

## IT Dep. LOTUS Company, Tehran, Iran Website Developer

Nov 2013 - Jun 2015

• Programmed and maintained company's website (lotuslaptop.com)

# IT Dep. KARMA Engineering Company, Iran

Nov 2011 - Nov 2013

- Technical Support
- Maintained communication networks, and resolved any technical issues
- Provided 24\*7 level one support over 50 clients

## Members and Honors

- Second best graduate student paper award, International Telemetry Conference, 2021.
- Member of IEEE Communication Society (ComSoc).
- Member of IEEE Communication Society (ComSoc).
- Member of IEEE Information Theory Society (ITSoc).
- Member of IEEE Electrical and Computer Engineering Honor Society, Eta Kappa Nu.
- Outstanding IT engineer in Huawei Technologies Company, 2017.
- Monthly star engineer in JYANE Company, 2016.

## Certificates and SKILLS

- IT Certificates:
  - o CompTIA A+ and Network+
  - o CCNA (Cisco Certified Network Associate)
  - o MCITP (Microsoft Certified IT Professional)
  - o HCNA (Huawei Certified Network Associate)
- Skills in computer networks:
  - o Install and configure network devices (Switch, routers, ...) and network troubleshooting
  - o Install and configure virtual networks with VMware ESX, VCenter
  - o Knowledge in Cloud Computing Architecture such as AWS, 2x (Parallels)
- Technical knowledge:
  - o Programming Language: C/C++/Python/Matlab
  - o Operating Systems: Microsoft Windows Client-Server/Linux
  - o Software development methodology: Scrum/RUP